<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Einar Holsbø</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Einar Holsbø</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Erlich administers the Hacker Hostel, a tech incubator where Richard, Big Head, Dinesh, and Gilfoyle live and work in exchange for 10 percent of their potential businesses. Erlich clings to his glory days, when he sold aviation start-up Aviato, a move that, at least in his mind, qualifies him to be a svengali lording over other tech nerds. He still drives a car emblazoned with multiple Aviato logos and smokes copious amounts of weed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Most violent show on earth</title>
      <link>/blog/2016-10-03-violence/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016-10-03-violence/</guid>
      <description>Warning from January, 2018: The statistics provided by SSB have changed a little since I made this post, for unknown reasons. Hence the text below might not be 100% accurate in terms of what the text says and what the data show. I have tried to tidy it up but I make no guarantees.
So I’m currently at a ten month reserach stay in Paris. I’m reluctant in the face of change, so I often think of home while I’m in my small apartment in a building with a slight mouse problem, or in my larger office with, astonishingly, also a slight mouse problem (unconfirmed).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neural network overengineering</title>
      <link>/blog/2016-08-24-neural-network-overengineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2016-08-24-neural-network-overengineering/</guid>
      <description>In my idle hours (ie when I should have been writing a paper), I came across this blog post where the author trained a neural netwok in the fine art of wine tasting. I am basically deep down a very lazy person, and from what little I understand of NNs, there are quite a few knobs to fiddle with, which really who has the time with all this untasted wine floating about?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>